<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BeCalm</string>
    <string name="menu_toast">Raise Toast</string>
    <string name="mn_it_add">Pie</string>
    <string name="btStartText">Start</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to BeCalm!</string>
    <string name="welcome_st">Your first step to a stress-free life</string>
    <string name="welcome_info">Please insert your info for a more personalized experience:</string>
    <string name="welcome_name">Name:</string>
    <string name="welcome_age">Age:</string>
    <string name="welcome_sex">Sex:</string>
    <string name="welcome_bt">Start</string>
    <string name="welcome_years">years</string>
    <string name="welcome_male">Male</string>
    <string name="welcome_female">Female</string>
    <string name="hiwTitle">How it Works?</string>
    <string name="hiw_st">A simple way to improve your Day</string>
    <string name="hiw_info">Just follow this steps to start improving your daily mood</string>
    <string name="hiw_step1">Step 1: </string>
    <string name="hiw_step1_msg">In the "Choose Device" page, select your Vital Jacket and hit the "Select" button. A message saying "Connected" should appear.</string>
    <string name="hiw_step2">Step 2: </string>
    <string name="hiw_step2_msg">On the start of your day, press the "Start" button on your main page to start monitoring your stress</string>
    <string name="hiw_step3">Step 3: </string>
    <string name="hiw_step3_msg">At the end of your day, press "Stop" in the same location</string>
    <string name="hiw_step4">Step 4: </string>
    <string name="hiw_step4_msg">Evaluate your stress levels and leave a comment about what made you feel that way</string>
    <string name="hiw_end_msg1">Doing this on a constant bases will help you to better understand your thoughts and emotions throughout the day</string>
    <string name="hiw_end_msg2">With that, you will be able to control your stress when subjected to different everyday scenarios</string>
    <string name="hiw_end_msg3">You can also do a quick measure of your stress levels whenever you feel like it in the "Instant Measurement" page</string>
    <string name="hiw_end_msg4">The comments that you leave everyday will be stored, so that you can review them whenever you want in the Homepage</string>
    <string name="hiw_end_msg5">Welcome to Your better Future :)</string>
    <string name="about_title">About the App</string>
    <string name="about_p1">You are already tired of hearing tons of tips to relieve stress and nothing really working out, right? Be calm that BeCalm is here to finally solve your problem ;)</string>
    <string name="about_p2">This app, together with VitalJacket, will help you recognize the patterns and habits in your daily life that induce stress, so you can manage them better in future situations, avoiding more stress.</string>
    <string name="about_p3">We are a team of four young students from the Faculty of Engineering of the University of Porto challenged to create this app under the Mobile Computing in Biomedical Engineering class.</string>
    <string name="about_p4">We would like to thank João Paulo Cunha and António Miguel Monteiro for teaching and advising us; and Biodevices S.A. for providing the VitalJacket, a heart monitor medical device built into a t-shirt used in our tests.</string>
</resources>